AJMALSHA SALIM

MERN Stack Developer



CONTACT

- 9539706416, 7306129332
- □ ajmalaj8085@gmail.com
- Trivandrum, Kerala, India
- ajmalsha.netlify.app
- ajmalsha-salim
- github.com/AjmalshaSalim

EDUCATION

Mar Ivanious Trivandrum

2020 - 2023 B.A. in History

COURSES

G Tec - 6 months

July 2022 - December 2022 Full Stack Development

FRONTEND SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind
- Ajax
- React
- Redux

PROFILE

A self-taught individual with 2 years of industrial experience, showcasing strong multitasking abilities and a dedicated work ethic. Possesses effective teamwork, problem-solving, and organizational skills. Willing to take on various responsibilities to support the team, known for being a reliable and committed collaborator with a diligent and resourceful approach.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

Trivolgic - Current

August 2024 - Present

- Project Discussion, Project Demostration
- Multiple Project Handling & Workload Balance

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

A2Z Alphabet Solutionz

August 2023 - July 2024

Project Planning, Documentation & Client Presentation

1 Year

- Team Contribution & Version Management
- Multi Tasking & Multiple Project Handling
- Time Management: Balances workload and meets deadlines efficiently

MERN STACK DEVELOPER INTERN

Brototype Packapeer Academy Pvt Ltd - 7 monthsDecember 2022 - July 2023

- Project Research, Documentation And Presentation
- UI/UX Designing & Schema Structuring (Database Design/Data Modeling)
- Communication Sections & Public Speaking
- Section To Improve Coding Standard & Typing Speed

BACKEND SKILLS

- Node Js
- Express
- Mongo DB
- MySQL
- REST API

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Github
- Hostinger
- AWS
- Postman
- Figma
- Canva

ADD-ON SKILLS

- Proficient in OOPS Concepts
- Knowledge in Data Structures
- Proficient in Material-UI for React application

LANGUAGES

- English
- Malayalam (Native)
- Hindi
- Arab (Read & Write)

HOBBIES

- Drawing & Designing
- Photo Editing

MASTER PROJECTS

GYMSOFT

GYM MANAGEMENT SOFTWARE

Software Key Features -

- User, Gym Admin & Owner Interfaces
- Attendance Management
- Slot Management
- Enquiry Management & Followup
- Users, Trainers & Staff Management
- Equipment Management & Service Followup
- Salary Management
- Gym Plans & Fee Management
- Diet Plan Management
- Gym Branch Management
- Admin Task Reminder
- Attendance Through QR Code Scanner
- User Profile & Performance Tracking

FRESH BELLS

DIET BASED E-COMMERCE PLATFORM

website Key Features -

- User Profile & User Management
- Product Management
- Cart & Wishlist
- Order Management
- Add To Cart Without User Login
- Diet Plan Management
- Payment Integration

AGEIS RECRUITMENT

JOB RECRUITMENT PORTAL

website Key Features -

- User Management (Job Seeker)
- Client Management (Company)
- User Profile Incuding Skills & Resume
- Client Profile
- Job Management & Shortlisting
- Email Notifications